myblogu.com 2015-12-07

# MyBlogU Privacy Policy | MyBlogU

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your username, or email address.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your username, and email. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

We  do not share personally identifiable information (such as username and email) with other companies.

We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting. Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user.

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
info AT myblogu DOT com
